{
    "subject": "resource/Hummer_(video_game)",
    "predicate": "ontology/developer",
    "object": "resource/Sega",
    "human_readable": "Hummer is developed by Sega.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9268782734870911,
            "question": "When was the Hummer first developed by Sega?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665208220481873,
            "question": "Who developed the Hummer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6552719473838806,
            "question": "What company created the Hummer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5039952993392944,
            "question": "Is Sega known for developing vehicles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4498177468776703,
            "question": "What are some features of a Hummer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36070069670677185,
            "question": "What type of vehicle is a Hummer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3584967851638794,
            "question": "Is the Hummer a popular brand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3554804027080536,
            "question": "How successful has Sega been in developing vehicles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34258580207824707,
            "question": "Are there different models of Hummers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19309227168560028,
            "question": "Besides video games, what else does Sega make?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hummer is developed by Sega.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5363_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different models of Hummers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5363_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How successful has Sega been in developing vehicles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5363_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Hummer a popular brand?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5363_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5363_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Hummer\" was a game developed and published by Sega, supporting the statement that it was developed by Sega."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}